A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, RG 2 FA433
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office of the Messieurs Rockefeller (OMR) Files, 1878-1972; bulk; 2; 21 Cubic Feet
  - Correspondence, 1919-1962, 1964; 1; 6 box(es)
    - General - Marston, Randolph, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      Business and other issues, including Vitarama, Fomento, McDonnell-Platt-LePage merger, Eastern Airlines, New York Zoological Society, South Puerto Rico Sugar, Cairns Corporation. William Coles and American-Colombian survey.
    - General - Matousek, Otakar and Bozema, 1932-1946 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      Includes four black-and-white snapshots of young boys, probably Otakar Matousek's sons George and Milos. Dates penciled on back of photos: 1931, 1935, 1938, 1939. Probably enclosed with Matousek correspondence.
    - General - Murray - Osborn, 1943-1960 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      Alphabetical. Murray, Albert K., 1948-1960 [see also MSKCC - Staff (Alphabetical) - Rhoads, C.P., 1950-1950, for Murray to LSR, September 5, 1956]; Osborn, Fairfield, and Marjorie, 1943-1957
    - General - Outhwaite, Leonard, 1939-1961 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - General - Prentice, Mary Adeline (Madeline), 1935 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - General - Rickenbacker, Eddie, 1949-1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - General - S-Z (Box 4, Folder 47)
      Alphabetical. Soldwedel, Frederic, and Florence, 1950-1961; Weil, Peter, 1941-1945; Zorach, William, 1952-1959
    - Family - Calendar of LSR - Family Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Handwritten calendar of correspondence contained in this series between LSR and his parents, siblings, and aunt.
    - Family - Aldrich, Lucy Truman, [1935]-1951, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby "Babs", [1934]-1950 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, 1920-1933 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, 1934-1947 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich (Estate), 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich and John D., Jr., 1927-1928, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Family - Rockefeller, David, 1937-1949 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1920-1932 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1933-1936 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1933-1936 (Box 4, Folder 57 A)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 58A)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 59A)
      Closed
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 60)
      Includes 8 x 10 black-and-white photograph of JDR Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller with a soldier, a sailor, and a marine, taken at opening of the U.S.O. building in Williamsburg, circa May 1943. Enclosed in JDR Jr. to LSR, May 26, 1943.
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 60A)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 61A)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1951-1960 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1951-1960 (Box 5, Folder 62A)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd, 1930-1959 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd, 1930-1959 (Box 5, Folder 63A)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1931-1956 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Winthrop, [1935]-1941 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Mail Log, 1953-1961 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      2 oversized ledgers (1953-1957 November; 1957 November-1961 July)
      Mail received and disposition
    - Mail Log, 1961 June-December (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Mail Log (Oversized file), 1953-1961July (Box 52)
      2 Ledger volumes, 1953-1961 July, recording incoming mail (date received, author, subject, and disposition).
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, to Lucy Greene, 1888 January 15 (Box 54, Folder 715)
      Custodial History
      Letter found with original letters and telegrams to Laurance S. Rockefeller from Abby Aldrich Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1920-1933, in the papers of LSR's associate Fred Smith. Material appears to have been lent for copying and never returned. The correspondence has been removed from Smith's papers and added to the correspondence series in RG 2. This one early letter is unique among these items in not being directly addressed to LSR.
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich (Telegrams), 1926-1933 (Box 54, Folder 716)
      Letters and telegrams from Abby Aldrich Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1920-1933, were found among the papers of associate Fred Smith, to whom they appear to have been lent for copying, as he was working on a biography of LSR. There is a full set of copies of these letters in Smith's files. The originals have been removed from Smith's papers and added to the Correspondence series in RG 2. We have not attempted to integrate them with the other correspondence files for Abby Aldrich and John D. Rockefeller, Jr., but they complete these files, which for AAR, especially, consist largely of typed copies.
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, 1920-1921, 1923, 1925-1933, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 717)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, 1920-1932 (Box 54, Folder 718)
    - Family - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich, Undated (1920-1933) (Box 54, Folder 719)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Telegrams), 1928-1933 (Box 54, Folder 720)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1920-1923 (Box 54, Folder 721)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1925-1928 (Box 54, Folder 722)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1929-1930 (Box 54, Folder 723)
    - Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1931-1933 (Box 54, Folder 724)
  - Personal Papers, 1910-1962; 2; 13 box(es)
    Related Materials
    Materials on LSR's interests and activities are also found in the subject series of the Office of the Messieurs Rockefeller (OMR) records.
    The Personal Papers series contains files relating to LSR's personal life and activities: club memberships, contributions, real estate and houses, boats and other personal property, interests and trips, plus a few files on his education, marriage, and naval service. Other materials include condolence letters LSR received on the deaths of his parents Abby Aldrich Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. A few files concern memorials to AAR and JDR, Jr.
    Significant biographical material includes a draft of an unpublished biography of LSR by his associate Frederik Smith, and LSR's Activity Lists, an annual detailing of his business, philanthropic, and social interests, activities, and memberships, which was compiled for the Rockefeller family office. The Awards file includes awards LSR received from the Belgian Congo, for his conservation work, and for his work on behalf of cancer research and treatment. The Jury Duty file concerns in particular LSR's service in 1953-1954 as foreman of a Special Grand Jury empanelled to investigate waterfront crime.
    Contribution files document LSR's philanthropic contributions for the period 1935 to 1961, and include annual and comprehensive statements of his contributions and giving program. There is also one file detailing LSR's Conservation Benevolences from 1942 to 1963.
    A large proportion of this series concerns LSR's residences in New York City and Pocantico Hills, New York, and his boats. The files on both subjects show something of LSR's early and continuing interest in new technologies. LSR built a steel house on the Rockefeller family's Pocantico Hills estate (the Arcy Corporation failed in the middle of construction, which accounts for the large volume of correspondence). The Pocantico Hills House files (and the Office Furnishings file) also document LSR's interest in furnishings by the Finnish designer Alvar Aalto. The Boats files include correspondence and designs concerning aluminum-hulled boats, a 1941 proposal for concrete barges, and discussions of radios, life vests, and other equipment. Files on the Dauntless concern the yacht LSR used to commute between Tarrytown, New York and his Rockefeller Center office.
    The Aviation Interests files relate to LSR's wartime service with the Production Division of the U.S. Navy's Bureau of Aeronautics and document his continuing personal and business interest in aviation operations and innovation in the postwar years. The files include memoranda and reports on various airline corporations, inspection visits, aviation policy, and corporate offerings.
    LSR assumed his grandfather John D. Rockefeller's seat on the New York Stock Exchange as of August 5, 1937. The Brokerage Business files concern his membership on the exchange and administrative aspects of his business, but also include some materials on stock offerings and investment opportunities.
    The Schools files concern primarily LSR's enrollment and study at Princeton University, and include a copy of his senior thesis and some research notes. There is also a small file concerning his years at Harvard Law School.
    Other files concern Paintings and Works of Art, including a file on paintings of military aviation by Henry Farré, which LSR acquired for the Air Force Academy. The Paintings files and the Trips files help document LSR's friendship with artists Paul Maze and André Dunoyer de Segonzac. The Trips file for the Belgian Congo, 1949, includes LSR's itinerary for the opening of the textile factory, Filtisaf, which he had helped to establish.
    The Personal Papers series presents a very uneven record of LSR's life and activities, particularly for the period up through the mid-1940s. Personal papers in the as yet unprocessed RG 1 document more completely LSR's early education, college years, marriage, naval service, and early interests.
    - Activity Lists, 1935-1961 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      Annual listing of LSR's business, philanthropic, and social activities and related memoranda
    - Activity Lists, 1935-1961 (Box 5, Folder 68A)
    - Addresses, 1951-1957 (May) (Box 5, Folder 69)
      Speeches and correspondence concerning them
      See Speech File.
    - Addresses, 1957 (September) (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Addresses, 1958-1959 (September) (Box 5, Drawer 71)
    - Addresses, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 71A)
      Restricted.
    - Addresses, 1959 (October-December) (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Addresses, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Allowance, 1925-1934 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - American Air Legion Air Service Post Awards, 1956, 1959, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 75)
      LSR received award in 1959
    - Apartments - 115 East 67th Street - General, 1935-1952 (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 6, Folder 76)
      Safe; Charles Prendergast paintings; expenditures on apartment and furnishings
    - Apartments - 115 East 67th Street - Lease and Rent Payments, 1938, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      Cover letters for leases; coop conversion; lease extension
      Memos concerning air-conditioner in Apartments - 834 Fifth Avenue - General folder.
    - Apartments - 834 Fifth Avenue - General, 1947-1961 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      W. T. Grant seeking apartment; renovation costs; air-conditioner; terrace plantings
    - Apartments - 834 Fifth Avenue - Entertainment Systems, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Apartments - 834 Fifth Avenue - Holmes Electric Protective Company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      Empty folder.
    - Apartments - Properties Offered, 1939-1947 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Aviation Interests - General, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Aviation Interests - General, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      Ed Aldrin and Verville trainer; Clarence B. Healy; Richard Gruenberg, Spohn Magneto; Malcolm McAlpin; Richard W. Courts, Jr.; Brewster Aeronautical Corp. and Hayes Airport Accessories Corp.
    - Aviation Interests - General, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      GE Air ResearchDemonstration; Charles W. Newhall; LSR tour of airplane factories; Airline Terminal Corp.
    - Aviation Interests - General, 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      Western Air Lines; Don McLean memorandum on aviation policy; Harper Woodward on United Helicopters; Courlandt and Robert Gross, Lockheed; LSR association with New York Airways
    - Aviation Interests - General, 1952-1961 (Box 6, Folder 86)
      Glenn L. Martin Co.; Harper Woodward memorandum on helicopter operations in DC area; William Lewis reports on aviation safety and on European trip; Barish-Vortex Ring Parachute; Vertol and Japanese; Robert C. Bates memorandum on NASA; Kenneth Chorley and KLM service; Karl Clarke and Republic Aviation Corp.; Auriema Corp. Includes color snapshot of Grumman Mallard airplane, enclosed in Joseph C. Barta (William C. Wold Associates) to LSR, May 28, 1957. See also Personal Papers – Trips – General, 1956-1961, for LSR visits to Pentagon on behalf of Vertol, 1957.
    - Aviation Interests - Printed Material, 1938-1947, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Aviation Interests - Printed Material (Oversized file), 1938, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 703)
      Article on Eastern Air Lines' 10th Anniversary, IBM Business Machines, 1938 April 28; Aviation Design Progress [SB-12 helicopter], 1956.
    - Aviation Interests - Smith Barney Company, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      Memoranda on airline investment offerings. Correspondents: William Barclay Harding, Harper Woodward, LSR.
    - Awards and Decorations, 1950-1967 (Box 7, Folder 89)
      Ordre Royal du Lion (Belgian Congo); Conservation Service Award; Professional League of Virgin Islanders; Clement Cleveland Award; Princeton. Memoranda on Rockefeller support for Belgium and for cancer research.
    - Biography - Biographical Sketches, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, 1981, Undated (Box 7, Folder 91)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. File includes letter from Fred Smith to Joseph Ernst, May 12, 1981.
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Prologue and Chapters 1 - 3
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 7, Folder 92)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapters on Lincoln School, Princeton, Marriage and early career.
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapters 4-6
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 7, Folder 93)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapters on Venture Capital, conservation interest, and Grand Teton National Park.
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapters 7 - 9
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapters on 1940s-1950s, Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc.
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapters 10-12
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapters on Resorts and National Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapters 13-14
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 7, Drawer 96)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapter on Memorial Hospital
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapter 15
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 8, Folder 97)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapters on Memorial Hospital, Rockefeller brothers, 1960s
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapters 16-18
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 8, Folder 98)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapters on White House Conference on Natural Beauty; Adirondack Preserve; Hudson River Valley Commission
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapters 19-21
    - Biography - Fred Smith Working Manuscript, Undated (Box 8, Folder 99)
      890-page manuscript by LSR associate, M. Frederik Smith. Chapters include discussions of Adirondacks, Woodstock, JY Ranch
      "Search for Fulfillment: Notes on the Life and Times of John D. Rockefeller's Third Grandson,"" Chapters 22-23 and Epilogue page
    - Birthday Greetings, 1948-1961 (Box 8, Folder 100)
      Includes several telegrams from Eddie Rickenbacker.
    - Boats - General, 1937-1939 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Boats - General, 1940-1941 March (Box 8, Folder 102, Drawer E11, Drawer 56)
      Design for 41-foot fast passenger boat, for possible use in Venezuela; 79th Street boat basin, New York City
    - Boats - General, 1941 September; Still Images: 3 black-and-white 8.5" x 11" prints. (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 8, Folder 103)
      Concrete Shipbuilding Co., Inc., Proposal for the Construction of Concrete Barges Shipshape without Crew Design for the United States Maritime Commission, September 29, 1941.
    - Boats - General, 1946-1961 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Boats - Dauntless - General, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 105, Drawer E11, Drawer 56)
      See also Boats - New Boat. Correspondence mainly with Olin J. Stephens II of Sparkman & Stevens, concerning design, contracts, costs, and equipment of Dauntless, a 62-foot Waterline aluminum commuting yacht, Sparkman & Stevens design 621
    - Boats - Dauntless - General, 1947-1949; Still Image: one black-and-white 7" x 9" print. (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 8, Folder 106)
      See also Boats - New Boat. Correspondence mainly with Olin J. Stephens II of Sparkman & Stevens, concerning design, contracts, costs, and equipment of Dauntless, a 62-foot Waterline aluminum commuting yacht, Sparkman & Stevens design 621. Includes photograph of LSR docking the "Dauntless" at Tarrytown, June 1948.
    - Boats - Dauntless - General, 1950-1961; Still Image: black-and-white 8" x 10" glossy print. (Box 9, Folder 107)
      See also Boats - New Boat. Correspondence mainly with Olin J. Stephens II of Sparkman & Stevens, concerning design, contracts, costs, and equipment of Dauntless, a 62-foot Waterline aluminum commuting yacht, Sparkman & Stevens design 621. Includes photograph of "Dauntless," enclosed in letter to LSR from James E. Light, Bull Insular Line, Inc., February 25, 1953.
    - Boats - Dauntless - Inventories and Maintenance, 1947-1950 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Boats - Hobo (Charter), 1955 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Boats - Insurance, 1947-1958 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Boats - New Boat, 1945 (Drawer E11, Drawer 56, Box 9, Folder 111)
      See also Boats - Dauntless - General
    - Boats - Sea Beast (I), 1938 (Box 9, Frame 112)
    - Boats - Sea Beast (II), 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      Chris-Craft Cruiser
    - Boats - Squirrel, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      Lightning Class sailboat, for Camp Canaras
    - Boats - Taxter, Thomas, 1938-1945, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Boats - Whirlwind - General, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Drawer 116, Drawer E11, Drawer 56)
    - Boats - Whirlwind - General, 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Boats - Whirlwind - Loan and Gift of, 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 118)
      Given to the U. S. Government
    - Boats (Oversized file), 1945, 1949, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 704)
      Blueprints of Paramount Rubber Company products, 1949; drawing of welded propeller shaft strut, 1959; blueprint drawing for 63 foot offshore cruiser, 1945
      Dauntless; New Boat
    - Brokerage Business - New York Stock Exchange Seat - General, 1937-1940 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Brokerage Business - New York Stock Exchange Seat - General, 1941-1949, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Brokerage Business - New York Stock Exchange Seat - Lionel D. Edie and Company, 1937-1941 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Brokerage Business - Stock Offerings, 1944-1947 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Christmas Card Lists, 1944-1949, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 123)
      Sent and received. Lists for 1957-1959 were removed from Box 15, folder 205 (Rockefeller, John D., Jr.: Condolences [Lists]).
    - Clippings, 1934-1959 (Box 9, Folder 124)
      Princeton Summer Camp; article on Hog Island, 1937; Princeton-St. Paul's School hockey
    - Clubs - General, 1934-1961 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Clubs - General (Alphabetical), 1938-1960 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      Bath Club, Cotton Bay Club, Manursing Island Club, University Club
    - Clubs - Boone and Crockett Club, 1950-1961 (Box 10, Folder 127)
      American Museum of Natural History
    - Clubs - Brook Club, 1944-1961 (Box 10, Folder 128)
      111 East 54th Street, New York
    - Clubs - Camp Fire Club of American, 1941-1958 (Box 10, Folder 129)
      LSR elected a member in 1946
    - Clubs - Ivy Club (Princeton), 1939-1960 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Clubs - Ivy Club (Princeton), 1958 (Box 10, Folder 130 A)
    - Clubs - Links Club, 1955-1961 (Box 10, Folder 131)
      Links Golf Club, Roslyn, New York
    - Clubs - Seawanhaka Corinthian Yacht Club, 1947-1959 (Box 10, Folder 132)
      Oyster Bay, New York
    - Contributions - General, 1921, 1935-1943 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Contributions - General, 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Contributions - General, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Contributions - General, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Contributions - General, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - Contributions - Benevolence Statements, 1937-1948 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Contributions - Benevolence Statements, 1949-1961 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Contributions - Conservation Benevolences, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 140)
      Statements of contributions to Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. and to the American Conservation Association, 1942-1963.
    - Contributions - Conservation Benevolences, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 140 A)
    - Dogs, 1936-1940, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Employees - General, 1941-1960 (Box 11, Folder 142)
      Insurance and other benefits
    - Employees - General, 1941-1960 (Box 11, Folder 142 A)
      Restricted - Personnel files.
    - Employees - Bodine, William, 1937-1971 (Box 11, Folder 143)
      Restricted - Personnel file.
    - Engagement and Wedding Letters, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 144)
      Includes wedding congratulations.
    - Family Office (Confidential) - General, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Family Office (Confidential) - Charitable Gifts Code Memorandum, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 146)
      Tax advice concerning charitable gifts of securities of controlled corporations.
    - Fishers Island - General, 1949-1960 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Fishers Island - General, 1952, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 147 A)
    - Fishers Island - General, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 148)
      Sale of property.
    - Fishers Island - Contributions, 1950-1961 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Fishers Island - Fishers Island Country Club, 1950-1961 (Box 11, Folder 150)
      LSR on board of governors, 1954-1961.
    - Fishers Island - Snow Property Purchase, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Florida, 1950-1959 (Box 11, Folder 152)
      Property and rental offers
    - Gifts, Savings, and Credits, 1910-1950 (Box 11, Drawer 153)
      Gifts from JDR, Sr. and JDR, Jr.
    - Gifts, Savings, and Credits, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 153 A)
    - Invitations, 1948-1961 (Box 11, Folder 154)
      Social and professional invitations for luncheons and dinners, benefits, speaking engagements, committee meetings, etc.